In our code, we're going to initialize the adapter within the placeholder
fragment on create view method. Because that's where we want the list view to
be populated with data. We're using a array adapter, and we can initialize it
with four parameters. A context, the ID of a list item layout,
the ID of a text view within that list item layout, as well as a list of data.
We'll go through each of these parameters one by one now. First, for
context. It contained global information about the App environment.
It allows us to access system services and resources, as well as the application
specific resources that we've defined. We use the fragments containing activity
as the context. So, we're going to call getActivity for our parameter here.
Since the adapter needs to know the layout for each list item, and
needs some reference to the XML layouts that we've defined. The r.java class is
a generated file that creates human readable identifiers for our resources. For
the list item layout, we refer to it in code as r.layout.list_item forecast.
This was the name of the XML file that we created earlier. Next,
the array adapter needs to know how to take the weather forecast string and
set that to be displayed in a text view. So you pass in the ID of the text view
that we defined earlier, in the list item layout. Even though these two resource
IDs look similar, one starts with R.layout while the other starts with R.id.
R.layout refers to a layout file, while an ID refers to a specific [UNKNOWN]
element with the matching ID attribute. And lastly, we pass in a week forecast,
which is the array list of forecast data that we defined earlier.
Now go ahead and initialize your adapter. Check this box when you're done.